William Berry Hartsfield papers, circa 1860s-1983
Emory University
- Memorabilia, 1930s-1972, Series 9; Boxes 66-71, OP 77
  - Autographed picture, Rebo the clown, Nani Darnell, Mark Wilson, "Magic Kingdom of Alakazam," CBS, [1960-1965] (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Bumper sticker, "Arnall for Governor," undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Business card, Hartsfield, William B. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Business card, Reitz, Josef, Coca-Cola, Frankfurt/ Main, Germany, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Moses Cox files, 1946-1954, Series 10; Boxes 72-78
  This series contains subject files and correspondence belonging to Moses Cox from 1946-1954. The series contains very little material directly to or from Hartsfield. Cox was associated with the Georgia State Highway Department and the American Society of Civil Engineers and involved in Atlanta roadway planning and construction during the Hartsfield administration from the 1920s through the 1960s. Correspondence, memorandums, cost estimates, reports, and plans document parking, traffic, roadway planning and construction. Federal funding for roadway construction, safety reports, and bond commission activity, the Atlanta Expressway, land purchases for roadway development, and water services for new roadways are all topics covered in this series. The secretarial files are Cox's correspondence, organized by last name, from his time as secretary of the Joint Bond Commission.
  - Alphabetical files
  - Atlanta Traffic Commission, 1950-1953 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Transportation trip (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Commissioners of Roads and Revenues, 1926-1930 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Construction estimates, undated - 1953 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Donaldson, Clark, correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Audiovisual materials, 1960, 1971, Series 11; Box 79
  This series consists of audiovisual material related to Hartsfield. The series contains two items: an audio recording of the 1971 Shining Light Award originally broadcast of WSB radio and a film of Hartsfield's retirement from politics in 1960.
  Restrictions on Access
  Use copies have not been made for all of the audiovisual series at this time. Researchers must contact MARBL in advance for access to these materials.
  - Hartsfield's retirement, (film), June 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Shining Light Award Ceremonies, honoring William B. Hartsfield, WSB Radio, June 8, 1971 [digitized; filename 7805] (Box 79, Folder 2)
Index of Selected Correspondents
Correspondence with prominent local citizens, local, state and national politicians, Atlanta business leaders, and other well-known personalities is indexed here. Correspondence from Series 1: Personal Papers, Series 2:Correspondence, Series 3: Election files, Series 4: Subject Files, and Series 6: Personal Business files have been indexed. Index is to series or subseries number, folder title (if needed), and date. Please refer to the complete finding aid for box and folder number.
This is not an index to all correspondents represented in this collection. Indexed items include correspondence from particular individuals. Other materials (newspaper clippings, photographs) relating to the same individual have not been included.
Abram, Morris B. Series 2 - December 6, 1962, December 8, 1962, January 7, 1963, May 17, 1966, October 8, 1968, October 17, 1968 Series 4 - WLWA television station: August 13, 1962
Acheson, Dean Series 2 - July 2, 1968
Agnew, Spiro T. Series 2 - October 31, 1969